

EDCIL JONAS PENASO (415) 350-7517 San Francisco, CA edciljonas15@yahoo.com

Profile

A Culinary Professional with 8 years of experience running high level culinary teams.

Passionate about proficiency and attention to detail.

I am self taught Web Developer and am now seeking for opportunities in tech, related to Software Development where I can showcase and enhance my skills and be surrounded by like minded individuals to share and learn new skills and ideas. Recently got into finance with crypto day trading and technical analysis.

Tech Stacks

- HTML & CSS
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript
- React.js
- Node.js
- SQL
- MongoDB
- Mongoose
- Heroku
- Git
- Github

Portfolio

https://jonasp-portfolio.herokuapp.com/

EDUCATION

Complete Web Development Bootcamp 2021 by Dr. Angela Yu **Udemy**

Modern HTML & CSS(Including SASS) 2021 by Brad Traversy **Udemy**

Degree in Culinary Arts - 2011 MOST Institute Culinary School, Islacare Inc., Davao, Philippines

Certifications:

Complete Web Development Bootcamp 2021

Modern HTML & CSS(Including SASS) 2021

EXPERIENCE

Flagship Facility Services @ Facebook | San Francisco | California Jr. Sous Chef | 2019 - Current

Flagship Facility Services @ Facebook | San Francisco | California Line Cook, Lead Line Cook | 2018-2019

Birdsong | San Francisco | California Chef de Partie, Tournant | 2018

Gibson | San Francisco, California Chef de Partie, Tournant | 2017-2018

In Situ | San Francisco ,California Chef de Partie, Commis, Kitchen Runner, Kitchen Server | 2016- 2017

Selland's Market Café | East Sacramento, California Line Cook | 2014-2016

Marco Polo Hotel | Davao, Philippines Apprentice Chef | 2011